oneflare.com.au 2019-03-05

# Privacy Policy - Oneflare

_This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 26, 2014_

Oneflare Pty Ltd (ABN 26 154 482 283) (" **Oneflare** ", " **us** ", " **we** ") respects the privacy of all visitors to its website located at [http://www.oneflare.com.au](https://www.oneflare.com.au/) (" **Website** ").

**1\. Introduction**

This Privacy Policy explains how Oneflare Pty Ltd (ABN 26 154 482 283) (" **Oneflare** ", " **us** ", " **we** ") collects, uses, discloses and handles any personal information we collect from you, and how to contact us if you wish to access or correct your personal information, or complain about a breach of your privacy.

This privacy policy may be updated or amended from time to time for any reason to reflect our practices and obligations. This policy is incorporated by reference to our Terms of Use that apply to the services provided by Oneflare Pty Ltd. Any changes will take effect when they are made or posted on our website.

You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Oneflare complies with the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). All site users can find more information regarding privacy by visiting the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner’s website.

**2\. Collection and use of information**

When you interact with Oneflare via our website, over the phone, via email, via social media, by entering our promotions or participating in our surveys, we may collect personal information about you. Some information may be provided to us by clients, customers and contractors. This information can include your name, address, phone number, email address and credit card information.

We will only collect personal or private information necessary for any of our functions or activities. We retain the right to use or disclose your personal information that is required in the provision of information about or the promotion or delivery of Oneflare services to the user. This includes newsletters, promotional materials or direct marketing campaigns relevant to the services we offer. Oneflare abides by the Australian Privacy Principles in relation to direct marketing. We collect personal information submitted to our website through our registration forms, other web forms and cookies. The information collected through cookies is only used to track anonymous usage of our website. You may disable cookies in your browser settings. We may also obtain your personal information from other third parties that we interact with, where you have agreed with them that your information may be disclosed.

The information we collect helps us to deliver or advertise our services, understand and analyse online activity and collect important information that we consider important to managing the quality or content of the services we deliver. By engaging with our website and social media sites, you consent to us using and disclosing your information both for the purposes for which we have collected it and for other purposes related to marketing and advertising our services.

**3\. External Links**

Our website may contain links to external websites and those external websites may collect personal information about you. We do not hold the responsibility for the privacy practices of other businesses or the content of their website that are linked to our website.

**4\. Storage and security**

Oneflare places great importance on safeguarding the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We employ administrative, electronic and physical measures to ensure that your information is protected from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that hackers or unauthorised personnel will not gain access to your personal information despite our efforts. Ultimately, you are responsible for keeping your account information secure. Please contact us immediately if you become aware or have reason to believe there has been any unauthorised use of your personal information that we hold.

**5\. Accessing and correcting personal information**

Oneflare is committed to maintain accurate, relevant and appropriate information about our website users. You may request access for your personal information if it is in accordance to the Australian Privacy Principles. If you believe that any personal information we hold about you is inaccurate, incomplete, out-of-date or irrelevant, you may ask us to correct it or you can update the information by logging into your Oneflare account.

**6\. Complaints**

If you have a complaint about our Privacy Policy or believe that we have breached your privacy, please contact us via email at support@oneflare.com.au or via phone on 1300 886 118. We will investigate your complaint and attempt to resolve any breach that may have occurred in accordance with the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). If we are unable to satisfactorily resolve your concerns about our handling of your personal information, you can contact the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner.

**7\. Contact**

If you require further information regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at the following email address: support@oneflare.com.au

**8\. Acceptance**

You accept that your use of this website and any engagement with Oneflare includes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.
